Never forget a thing, again.

This is a long-term memory reminder. Do you
have something to remember forever? 
You are in the right place.

Get your memories together.

Privacy and Terms

By choosing “I agree” below you agree to Nevget’s Terms of Service.

You also agree to our Privacy Policy, which describes the personal 
information we collect, the purposes for which we collect it, 
and how it is stored, including these key points:

Data we collect and use when you use Nevget
	- When you sign up for a Nevget account we’ll ask for personal information, 
	  like your name and email address, to store with your account.
	- When you make or edit a reminder, for example, we may collect and use 
	  information about that activity – including information like the time you
	  created the reminder, reminder’s title, and hints.

You can change and remove your personal information anytime on the Account 
Settings.

Why we process it
We process this data for the purposes described in our policy, including to:
	- Help our services deliver more useful, customized content such as more 
	  relevant delayed notifications;
	- Improve the quality of our services and develop new ones;
	- Conduct analytics and measurement to understand how our services are 
	  used.

Storage of data
Nevget makes reasonable efforts to provide users with ways to access their 
personal information and to delete such data upon request. After a user requests 
that information be deleted, copies of the data will expire and be subsequently 
overwritten, unless a copy must be retained for legitimate business purposes or 
to comply with the law.


E-mail format is incorrect.

You can’t leave this empty.

[insert password restrictions]

These passwords don't match. Try again?